

# **ABHINANDAN KUMAR**

Full Stack Web Developer

#### **Contact Me**

**(** +917488026507

Sitamarhi, Bihar

Abhinandan Kumar

in abhinandan Kumar

PortFolio Link

### **Professional Summary**

A passionate Full Stack Web Developer with proficiency in javascript, ReactJs, ExpressJs, NodeJs, Data Structures, and Algorithms. Has 1200+ hours of coding experience. Is an Adaptable team player who is goal-oriented and solutionsfocused. Looking forward to utilizing his skillset and experience in creating a mark in the software industry and achieving organizational goals.

### **Technical Skills**

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | GitHub | Jsonserver | ReactJs | Redux | ChakraUI | NodeJs | Data Structures and Algorithm

### Soft Skills

Teamwork | Leadership Adaptability | Problem Solving

### **Education**

Full Stack Web Development(full time) Masai School, Bangalore July 2022 - Present

Mechanical Engineering(B.Tech.) Guru Nanak Dev Engineering College, Ludhiana, Punjab

August 2015 - June 2019

## **Professional Experience**

#### Unistal System Pvt. Ltd., Noida **Project Engineer**

April 2021 - July 2022

Key responsibilities:

- Worked in Oil and Gas pipeline construction
- Made plans for daily weekly and monthly work
- Made Measurement sheet and abstract of

### Pratham EPC Project Pvt Ltd., Surat **Assistant Planning Engineer**

September 2019 – March 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Worked in Oil and Gas pipeline construction
- · Make Daily, weekly, and monthly progress
- Make Measurement sheet and abstract of payment

### **Projects**

#### SkinStore.com - Clone



• SkinStore.com is an E-commerce Website that provides many skincare and luxury spa

A collaborative project built by a team of five members in six days.

Features: Navbar | Login & Sign Up | Sort | Filter | Remove | Add to cart | Checkout

Tech Stack: HTML | CSS | JavaScript |

#### Areas of Responsibility

- Led the team.
- Developed product page and added Sort, filter, add to cart & remove functionality
- Deployed on render and Netlify

#### Shine.com - Clone



• Shine.com is an online job portal & that also offers many courses for skills development.

An individual project was built and executed in five days.

Features: Navbar | Login & Sign Up | Sort | Filter | Remove | Add to cart | Checkout

Tech Stack: HTML | CSS | JavaScript |